https://www.roadtrek.com/privacy-policy/

You're all set!
Your message has been sent successfully.
OK
Our Models
2021 Play
2021 Play Get out and Play!
Two
Two
Up to Three
Up to Three
MSRP Starting at$104,986 usd$104,986USD$125,986 cdn$125,986CDN
Up to Three
MSRP Starting at$142,660 usd$142,660USD$162,960 cdn$162,960CDN
View Details
Build Your Own
2021 Zion
2021 Zion Someday starts now.
Five
Up to Three
MSRP Starting at$139,860 usd$139,860USD$160,860 cdn$160,860CDN
View Details
Build Your Own
2021 Zion SRT
2021 Zion SRT It's the little things that make life big.
Five
Up to Three
MSRP Starting at$132,860 usd$132,860USD$153,860 cdn$153,860CDN
Up to Five
MSRP Starting at$153,986 usd$153,986USD$174,986 cdn$174,986CDN
Up to Three
MSRP Starting at$167,986 usd$167,986USD$195,986 cdn$195,986CDN
View Details
Build Your Own
CS Adventurous – Available Summer 2021
CS Adventurous – Available Summer 2021 AVAILABLE SUMMER 2021
RS Adventurous – Available Summer 2021
RS Adventurous – Available Summer 2021 AVAILABLE SUMMER 2021
Careers
Currency:
Privacy Policy
While information is the cornerstone of our ability to provide superior service, our most important asset is our user’s trust. Your privacy is a top priority for all of us at Roadtrek Inc.
This Privacy Statement will outline how Roadtrek Inc. treats your personal information collected on our Web Site, including what type of personal information is gathered, how it is tracked, used and with whom the information is shared.
Your personal information is any information, recorded in any form, about you (e.g. name, address, phone number or e-mail address).
This Privacy Statement does not apply to the practices of companies that Roadtrek Inc. does not own or control, or to people that Roadtrek Inc. does not employ or manage.
If you have any questions, suggestions or concerns regarding our privacy statement, or accuracy of information please contact our Information System Manager at:
Email: info@roadtrekinc.com
Tel: 519-745-1160
Fax: 519-622-0505
Roadtrek Inc.
20 Tyler Street
Cambridge, ON
N1T 0E4
Information Collection and Use
In general NO personal information is collected from our visitors. You can freely visit roadtrek.com on the Internet without telling us who you are and without giving us any personal information about yourself.
The Internet site does record non-personal statistical information through the use of technologies referred to as “cookies and log files”. Such information is used to measure and monitor the use of our web site and to provide an enhanced on line experience.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data that the web site sends to your computer as an anonymous tag that identifies your computer but not you.
We only use non-persistent cookies that disappear when you shut down your browser. The cookies are used to distinguish between anonymous and authenticated users (dealers who log in to the dealer site).
Log Files
Log files are used to collect quantitative information, e.g.., total page views, most popular pages etc.
Profiles
A profile is stored information (collected through cookies, log files, etc.) on individual users that details their viewing preferences. Consequently collected information is tied to the users personally identifiable information to provide offers and improve the content of the site for the user.
Roadtrek Inc. does not profile users.
Personal Information Collection
The only personal information collected through our web site is information that you volunteer to provide. This personal information is requested on our Video / Brochure order form and on our Dealer Locator form. You must provide us with your contact information such as your name and shipping address.
This personal information is required in order for us to process our customer’s orders.
Personal Information Use
Roadtrek Inc. uses this personal information in order to fulfill your brochure or dealer requests.
Roadtrek Inc. uses third party service providers to process these requests. These providers do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purpose.
The personal information is used to send your name and address to the dealers closest to you.
This personal information is used for Roadtrek Inc to occasionally send out information relating to new product introductions, special offers, consumer surveys; (Participation in surveys is completely voluntary), etc.
Roadtrek Inc respects your privacy. If you do not wish to have your information used for the purpose(s) described in this statement, you can elect to do so.
Information for Business Partners
If you represent a Roadtrek Inc. Business Partner (Dealer), you may visit the Roadtrek Inc’s web site intended specifically for Dealers.
Roadtrek Inc. may use information provided on the Dealer web site to administer and develop our business relationship with you, the Business Partner you represent, and Roadtrek Inc. Dealers generally.
Roadtrek Inc. may use your information to send you details of Roadtrek Inc’s Business Partner programs. Roadtrek Inc. may also share certain contact information with other Business Partners (subject to any confidentiality obligations that may exist), Roadtrek Inc’s customers or Roadtrek Inc’s prospects. In connection with a particular transaction or program, we may also contact you as part of customer satisfaction surveys or for market research purposes.
Links
Roadtrek Inc’s web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Roadtrek Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices of these linked sites. Roadtrek Inc. encourages all our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each web site visited that collects personally identifiable information.
This Privacy Statement applies solely to the information collected by the Roadtrek Inc. web site.
Disclosures Required by Law
Please be aware that in certain circumstances, Roadtrek Inc. may be required to disclose personal information we hold pursuant to judicial authorizations (e.g. subpoenas, warrants, orders) or where required by law.
Notification of Changes
If Roadtrek Inc. decides to change our Privacy Statement, we will post those changes on the home page and other places deemed appropriate. Any changes will be posted so that our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
